worldticket.net 2019-03-29

# Privacy Policy - Worldticket

Topics:

  * What information do we collect about you?
  * How will we use the information about you?
  * What is the legal basis for collecting personal information?
  * Who will receive personal information about you?
  * How long will we keep your personal information?
  * What are your rights?
  * Security safeguards
  * Marketing
  * Cookies
  * Other websites
  * Changes to our privacy and cookie policy
  * How to contact us

**What information do we collect about you?**  
This privacy and cookie policy covers all personal information about you that we collect, use and otherwise process in connection with your relationship with WorldTicket as a customer, potential customer or job applicant.

By “Personal Information” we mean information about you, such as your name and contact details and about your access to our websites.

We collect information about you when you use our contact form, register with us or place an order for products or services, subscribe to our newsletter, enter into a contract with us or send a job application. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies.

We do not collect any special categories (sensitive) of personal data, such as health, religious or political data.

**How will we use the information about you?**  
The personal information is used to provide information, products, news, business arrangements and other business-related activities in your service and in case of job applications, to process your application and to comply with any legal obligations.

What is the legal basis for collecting personal information?  
The handling of personal information is in accordance with EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) as stated in REGULATION (EU) 2016/679 OF THE EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT AND OF THE COUNCIL and applicable national law.

We only collect necessary information to provide you with the services you request from us, to perform according to a contract or prepare for doing so, to pursue legitimate interests or requirements needed according to law. If we don’t get access to your information we may not be able to provide you with our services.

Who will receive personal information about you?  
Transfer of your personal information will only be for specific purposes as to provide a seamless customer experience and we will ensure that the security is at the highest possible level.  
Depending on the services you want us to provide we may transfer your personal data to countries outside the European Union/EEA in order to perform a contract with you. In some cases, you may have to give us consent and you should be aware that the security in such cases may not be the same as in your country of origin. The transfer will be in accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).  
We share your personal information with Softlayer and Itadel, who is hosting our website. The hosting is provided in Softlayer (Europe/USA/China) and Itadel (Denmark).  
How long will we keep your personal information?  
We only keep your data as long as needed for the purpose of the data collection, e.g. to fulfill the obligations to deliver the services, or that is needed for legal purposes. We will as a general rule, delete data after 5 years, unless there are specific reasons for keeping them for a longer period.

If you are a job applicant we will delete your application and other information you may have provided 3 months after the hiring process has ended.

Personal data in connection with surveys, competitions etc. will be deleted within 1 month after the result has been announced.

**What are your rights?**  
Please contact us if you want to have access, incorrect data corrected or deleted, withdraw a consent or raise a complaint.

There may be restrictions or limitations to these rights which will be considered in the specific circumstances.

Please also see our cookie policy.

Security safeguards  
WorldTicket has implemented appropriate technical as well as organisational measures in order to safeguard the processing of your personal data. We have e.g. safeguards against loss or theft as well as unauthorised access and undue disclosure of personal data.

Examples of technical safeguards include encryption, “firewalls” and Secure Socket Layer (SSL). See further details of these technical safeguards for personal data collected through our website here.

As an example of a procedural safeguard, WordTicket has implemented various authentication procedures internally and with our external service providers that may involve us requesting various personal particulars from you in order to verify your identity before we process your request for a particular service, product or transaction. If you have any concerns about security, you should contact us.

**Marketing**  
We would like to send you information about products and services of ours and other companies in our group which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out later. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to other members of the WorldTicket family of coorperations. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please click here.

We don’t transfer or sell your personal information to any other third parties.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.

The first time you land on our website you will see a box with information on cookies. If you don’t accept cookies, there will be no cookies for statistics, but there will be a cookie remembering this choice. If you don’t want our website to leave any cookies at all, you will have to turn cookies off in your browser. It will then also not be possible to use any other features that requires that the website remembers your choices.

**Other websites**  
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy and cookie policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their privacy and cookie policies.

**Changes to our privacy and cookie policy**  
We keep our privacy and cookie policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. This privacy and cookie policy was last updated on 7th May 2018.

**How to contact us**  
WorldTicket is the data controller and you should at any time feel free to contact us if you have any question s about our privacy and cookie policy or information we hold about you:

WorldTicket A/S  
Kultorvet 11, 3rd Floor  
DK-1175 Copenhagen K  
Denmark  
Company register no. 29794626

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are not processing your personal data in accordance with the law you can complain to the Danish Data Protection Agency. www.datatilsynet.dk/english
